SiChao Chen

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

c2505384203@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/sichao-chen

Summary

I am a Computer Science professional with expertise in Full Stack Web Development. My portfolio boasts multiple successful website projects catering to a diverse array of real-world businesses. Experienced in Python, Java, HTML, CSS, Javacript, PHP, and MySQL.

Github: https://github.com/Ocean48

Experience

Content Specialist

PharmAchieve

Apr 2021 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Assisted with online mock OSCE exams.

m Peer Leader

TNG Community Services

Sep 2016 - Jun 2017 (10 months)

Education



Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

Sep 2020 - May 2024

Received Dean's Honour Roll every year after starting computer science degree

Researched in artificial narrow intelligence, machine learning, and tree search techniques (Monte Carlo tree search - MCTS)

Licenses & Certifications

Cisco Certified Network Associate Routing and Switching (CCNA) - Cisco Networking Academy

CPA: Programming Essentials in C++ - C++ Institute

Introduction to Internet of Things - Cisco Networking Academy

in Software Architecture Foundations - LinkedIn

Skills

Leadership • Python (Programming Language) • Microsoft Office • Teamwork • C++ • C (Programming Language) • Java • Full-Stack Development • MySQL

Honors & Awards



Dean's Honour Roll, Faculty of Science - University of Windsor

Dean's Honour Roll recipient for every school year starting second year